Boston Dispensary Records MS214
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Employment records, 1920 -- 1967; MS214.007; 6.0 Linear Feet
  - Employee personnel files, 1920 -- 1967; MS214.007.001
    - Larigill, Etta, 1926; MS214.007.004.00360 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Larkin, Catherine, 1956; MS214.007.004.00361 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lawler, Michael, 1934; MS214.007.004.00362 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Leary, Catherine, 1933; MS214.007.004.00363 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Leary, Marion, 1937; MS214.007.004.00364 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lee, Cornelia, 1962; MS214.007.004.00365 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lee, Imelda, 1963; MS214.007.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Lehrman, Theresa, 1965; MS214.007.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Leo, Mary, 1928; MS214.007.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Leonard, Evelyn, 1941; MS214.007.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Leslie, George, 1933; MS214.007.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Levens, Ernest, 1939; MS214.007.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - Levine, Franne, 1967; MS214.007.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Helen, 1945; MS214.007.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Jane, 1931; MS214.007.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Lewis, Ora, 1937; MS214.007.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Lipman, Lee, 1943; MS214.007.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Liscum, Jane, 1949; MS214.007.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Lloyd, Elizabeth, 1961; MS214.007.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Ludy, Dorothy, 1932; MS214.007.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Ludy, Helen, 1939; MS214.007.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, Edward, 1926; MS214.007.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, Nancy, 1967; MS214.007.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Macdonald, Jean, 1961; MS214.007.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Mackenzie, Catherine, 1959; MS214.007.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Mackinnon, Alice, 1961; MS214.007.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Macksey, Noel, 1927; MS214.007.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - MacLaughlin, James, 1929; MS214.007.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Maclean, Olive, 1929; MS214.007.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Makaren, Selma, 1963; MS214.007.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Mallows, Nellie, 1921; MS214.007.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - Mann, Josephine, 1927; MS214.007.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Marino, Lorraine, 1963; MS214.007.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - Mark, Teresa, 1931; MS214.007.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Marks, Alison, 1953; MS214.007.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - Maroney, Kathleen, 1960; MS214.007.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Martin, Helen, 1939; MS214.007.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Martin, Lucy, 1941; MS214.007.005.00032 (Box 5)
    - Martineau, Florence, 1954; MS214.007.005.00033 (Box 5)
    - Martorana, Jennie, 1921; MS214.007.005.00034 (Box 5)
    - Mason, Blanche, 1965; MS214.007.005.00035 (Box 5)
    - Mason, Jean, 1965; MS214.007.005.00036 (Box 5)
    - Masters, Susan, 1954; MS214.007.005.00037 (Box 5)
    - Mathewson, Ruth, 1930; MS214.007.005.00038 (Box 5)
    - McBride, Dorothy, 1943; MS214.007.005.00039 (Box 5)
    - McCarthy, Anne, 1956; MS214.007.005.00040 (Box 5)
    - McCarthy, Margaret, 1964; MS214.007.005.00041 (Box 5)
    - McCully, Shirley, 1963; MS214.007.005.00042 (Box 5)
    - McCusker, May, 1925; MS214.007.005.00043 (Box 5)
    - McDermott, Anne, 1967; MS214.007.005.00044 (Box 5)
    - McDonald, Mildred, 1921; MS214.007.005.00045 (Box 5)
    - McEachern, Catherine, 1961; MS214.007.005.00046 (Box 5)
    - McGuiness, Dorothy, 1938; MS214.007.005.00047 (Box 5)
    - McMahon, Catherine, 1961; MS214.007.005.00048 (Box 5)
    - McMahon, Elizabeth, 1923; MS214.007.005.00049 (Box 5)
    - McMahon, Mary, 1948; MS214.007.005.00050 (Box 5)
    - McPhee, Jeanette, 1960; MS214.007.005.00051 (Box 5)
    - McPherson, Ethel, 1964; MS214.007.005.00052 (Box 5)
    - Merrifield, Marian, 1943; MS214.007.005.00053 (Box 5)
    - Midelfart, Elise, 1933; MS214.007.005.00054 (Box 5)
    - Miethe, Anna, 1950; MS214.007.005.00055 (Box 5)
    - Millen, Alice, 1955; MS214.007.005.00056 (Box 5)
    - Millstein, Celia, 1934; MS214.007.005.00057 (Box 5)
    - Mitchell, Ida, 1936; MS214.007.005.00058 (Box 5)
    - Mitchell, Judith, 1960; MS214.007.005.00059 (Box 5)
    - Mogan, Alice, 1934; MS214.007.005.00060 (Box 5)
    - Moghadassy, Mahin, 1962; MS214.007.005.00061 (Box 5)
    - Moon, Murielle, 1949; MS214.007.005.00062 (Box 5)
    - Moore, Jeanne, 1946; MS214.007.005.00063 (Box 5)
    - Moorehouse, Janet, 1943; MS214.007.005.00064 (Box 5)
    - Moran, Kathleen, 1959; MS214.007.005.00065 (Box 5)
    - Morgan, Helen, 1952; MS214.007.005.00066 (Box 5)
    - Morris, Julia, 1946; MS214.007.005.00067 (Box 5)
    - Morrison, Alice, 1967; MS214.007.005.00068 (Box 5)
    - Morrow, Susanna, 1965; MS214.007.005.00069 (Box 5)
    - Morse, Mary, 1956; MS214.007.005.00070 (Box 5)
    - Morton, Louise, 1933; MS214.007.005.00071 (Box 5)
    - Mosher, Willard, 1960; MS214.007.005.00072 (Box 5)
    - Moss, Fred, 1925; MS214.007.005.00073 (Box 5)
    - Mueller, H. Peter, 1942; MS214.007.005.00074 (Box 5)
    - Mullin, Christine, 1964; MS214.007.005.00075 (Box 5)
    - Munroe, Hazel, 1938; MS214.007.005.00076 (Box 5)
    - Murphy, Doris, 1960; MS214.007.005.00077 (Box 5)
    - Murphy, Edna, 1924; MS214.007.005.00078 (Box 5)
    - Murphy, Esther, 1936; MS214.007.005.00079 (Box 5)
    - Nakamura, Naoko, 1961; MS214.007.005.00080 (Box 5)
    - Nanes, Ethel, 1944; MS214.007.005.00081 (Box 5)
    - Nason, Marie, 1940; MS214.007.005.00082 (Box 5)
    - Nestor, Helen, 1940; MS214.007.005.00083 (Box 5)
    - Newhoff, Jeanette, 1930; MS214.007.005.00084 (Box 5)
    - Newton, Beatrice, 1936; MS214.007.005.00085 (Box 5)
    - Nikerson, Marion, 1931; MS214.007.005.00086 (Box 5)
    - Norman, Anita, 1930; MS214.007.005.00087 (Box 5)
    - Norton, Leo, 1940; MS214.007.005.00088 (Box 5)
    - O'Brien, Margaret, 1928; MS214.007.005.00089 (Box 5)
    - O'Brien, Marie, 1945; MS214.007.005.00090 (Box 5)
    - O'Connell, Maureen, 1962; MS214.007.005.00091 (Box 5)
    - O'Donnell, Irene, 1954; MS214.007.005.00092 (Box 5)
    - O'Flaherty, Margaret, 1924; MS214.007.005.00093 (Box 5)
    - O'Flaherty, Mary, 1927; MS214.007.005.00094 (Box 5)
    - O'Keefe, Patricia, 1958; MS214.007.005.00095 (Box 5)
    - O'Neill, Grania, 1958; MS214.007.005.00096 (Box 5)
    - O'Rourke, Margaret, 1958; MS214.007.005.00097 (Box 5)
    - O'Sullivan, Mary, 1957; MS214.007.005.00098 (Box 5)
    - Oates, Alice, 1962; MS214.007.005.00099 (Box 5)
    - Odian, Charles, 1934; MS214.007.005.00100 (Box 5)
    - Ogden, Agnes, 1922; MS214.007.005.00101 (Box 5)
    - Olsen, Bernard, 1965; MS214.007.005.00102 (Box 5)
    - Orlando, Rose, 1930; MS214.007.005.00103 (Box 5)
    - Orlen, Ellen, 1958; MS214.007.005.00104 (Box 5)
    - Osgood, Margaret, 1934; MS214.007.005.00105 (Box 5)
    - Ostrom, Marianne, 1946; MS214.007.005.00106 (Box 5)
    - Owens, Mary, 1963; MS214.007.005.00107 (Box 5)
    - Paton, Constana, 1956; MS214.007.005.00108 (Box 5)
    - Patriquin, Grace, 1925; MS214.007.005.00109 (Box 5)
    - Pattelena, Jean, 1957; MS214.007.005.00110 (Box 5)
    - Patton, Marguerite, 1954; MS214.007.005.00111 (Box 5)
    - Paulding, Eunice, 1922; MS214.007.005.00112 (Box 5)
    - Peabody, Margery, 1932; MS214.007.005.00113 (Box 5)
    - Pearson, Harriet, 1933; MS214.007.005.00114 (Box 5)
    - Pease, Mary, 1931; MS214.007.005.00115 (Box 5)
    - Perkins, Ray, 1934; MS214.007.005.00116 (Box 5)
    - Perlmutter, Celia, 1928; MS214.007.005.00117 (Box 5)
    - Perry, Dorothy, 1949; MS214.007.005.00118 (Box 5)
    - Perry, Gertrude, 1926; MS214.007.005.00119 (Box 5)
    - Peters, Carolyn, 1967; MS214.007.005.00120 (Box 5)
    - Pett, Elizabeth, 1960; MS214.007.005.00121 (Box 5)
    - Pettengill, Miriam, 1934; MS214.007.005.00122 (Box 5)
    - Pexton, Margaret, 1942; MS214.007.005.00123 (Box 5)
    - Pfaffmann, Mary, 1946; MS214.007.005.00124 (Box 5)
    - Phillipps, Marion, 1946; MS214.007.005.00125 (Box 5)
    - Philpott, Carol, 1961; MS214.007.005.00126 (Box 5)
    - Picardi, Ralph, 1967; MS214.007.005.00127 (Box 5)
    - Pickett, Helena, 1949; MS214.007.005.00128 (Box 5)
    - Pilcher, Lewis, 1929; MS214.007.005.00129 (Box 5)
    - Pinette, Marsha, 1967; MS214.007.005.00130 (Box 5)
    - Poehlman, Mary, 1929; MS214.007.005.00131 (Box 5)
    - Poikonen, Ingrid, 1957; MS214.007.005.00132 (Box 5)
    - Poole, Rebecca, 1952; MS214.007.005.00133 (Box 5)
    - Poppe, John, 1962; MS214.007.005.00134 (Box 5)
    - Pothier, Mary, 1960; MS214.007.005.00135 (Box 5)
    - Potter, Marion, 1943; MS214.007.005.00136 (Box 5)
    - Poutasse, Annetta, 1943; MS214.007.005.00137 (Box 5)
    - Poverman, Rosemarie, 1955; MS214.007.005.00138 (Box 5)
    - Powers, Amelia, 1928; MS214.007.005.00139 (Box 5)
    - Poynter, Emily, 1948; MS214.007.005.00140 (Box 5)
    - Price, Beatrice, 1931; MS214.007.005.00141 (Box 5)
    - Price, Lovel, 1948; MS214.007.005.00142 (Box 5)
    - Pritchard, Marion, 1947; MS214.007.005.00143 (Box 5)
    - Proger, Evelyn, 1931; MS214.007.005.00144 (Box 5)
    - Pudolsky, Ruth, 1961; MS214.007.005.00145 (Box 5)
    - Ractliffe, Marjorie, 1941; MS214.007.005.00146 (Box 5)
    - Radford, Sharlene, 1962; MS214.007.005.00147 (Box 5)
    - Ramsdell, Helen, 1926; MS214.007.005.00148 (Box 5)
    - Rand, Katharine, 1940; MS214.007.005.00149 (Box 5)
    - Rapp, Sahra, 1929; MS214.007.005.00150 (Box 5)
    - Read, Helena, 1929; MS214.007.005.00151 (Box 5)
    - Rec, Phyllis, 1957; MS214.007.005.00152 (Box 5)
    - Reed, Robert, 1931; MS214.007.005.00153 (Box 5)
    - Reilly, Kathleen, 1941; MS214.007.005.00154 (Box 5)
    - Reinauer, Eva, 1947; MS214.007.005.00155 (Box 5)
    - Renaud, Constance, 1963; MS214.007.005.00156 (Box 5)
    - Reynolds, Elinor, 1930; MS214.007.005.00157 (Box 5)
    - Ricci, Rosaline, 1956; MS214.007.005.00158 (Box 5)
    - Rice, Cynthia, 1946; MS214.007.005.00159 (Box 5)
    - Rice, Elizabeth, 1927; MS214.007.005.00160 (Box 5)
    - Rice, Helen, 1932; MS214.007.005.00161 (Box 5)
    - Rich, Emma, 1929; MS214.007.005.00162 (Box 5)
    - Rich, Martha, 1945; MS214.007.005.00163 (Box 5)
    - Richardson, Kenneth, 1939; MS214.007.005.00164 (Box 5)
    - Richardson, Marianne, 1953; MS214.007.005.00165 (Box 5)
    - Riley, Jean, 1961; MS214.007.005.00166 (Box 5)
    - Robbins, Linda, 1962; MS214.007.005.00167 (Box 5)
    - Roberts, Edward, 1962; MS214.007.005.00168 (Box 5)
    - Roberts, Mary, 1928; MS214.007.005.00169 (Box 5)
    - Roche, Eleanor K., 1927; MS214.007.005.00170 (Box 5)
    - Roche, Eleanor N., 1959; MS214.007.005.00171 (Box 5)
    - Rodgers, Elinor, 1933; MS214.007.005.00172 (Box 5)
    - Rogers, Mary Ann, 1944; MS214.007.005.00173 (Box 5)
    - Rohe, Irene, 1955; MS214.007.005.00174 (Box 5)
    - Rose, Anne, 1950; MS214.007.005.00175 (Box 5)
    - Rose, Miriam, 1926; MS214.007.005.00176 (Box 5)
    - Rosenberg, Sylvia, 1932; MS214.007.005.00177 (Box 5)
    - Rosenbloom, Marion, 1944; MS214.007.005.00178 (Box 5)
    - Rosenblum, Rietta, 1931; MS214.007.005.00179 (Box 5)
    - Rosenthal, Helen, 1931; MS214.007.005.00180 (Box 5)
    - Rowe, Olia, 1958; MS214.007.005.00181 (Box 5)
    - Rubbica, Rosemary, 1955; MS214.007.005.00182 (Box 5)
    - Ruddy, Patricia, 1960; MS214.007.005.00183 (Box 5)
    - Ruggles, Helen, 1946; MS214.007.005.00184 (Box 5)
    - Russell, Ruth, 1964; MS214.007.005.00185 (Box 5)
    - Salmon, Irene, 1922; MS214.007.005.00186 (Box 5)
    - Salmonsen, Marie, 1957; MS214.007.005.00187 (Box 5)
    - Sano, Machteld, 1927; MS214.007.005.00188 (Box 5)
    - Santoro, Marie, 1931; MS214.007.005.00189 (Box 5)
    - Saudberg, Harold, 1923; MS214.007.005.00190 (Box 5)
    - Savage, Alice, 1920; MS214.007.005.00191 (Box 5)
    - Savignac, Bartholomew, 1939; MS214.007.005.00192 (Box 5)
    - Savinksy, Theresa, 1961; MS214.007.005.00193 (Box 5)
    - Schraffa, Angela, 1958; MS214.007.005.00194 (Box 5)
    - Schreiber, Margaret, 1926; MS214.007.005.00195 (Box 5)
    - Scott, Irene, 1958; MS214.007.005.00196 (Box 5)
    - Senecal, Althea, 1942; MS214.007.005.00197 (Box 5)
    - Severson, Eliza, 1938; MS214.007.005.00198 (Box 5)
    - Shaffer, Emily, 1951; MS214.007.005.00199 (Box 5)
    - Shaw, Caroline, 1944; MS214.007.005.00200 (Box 5)
    - Shea, Marjorie, 1947; MS214.007.005.00201 (Box 5)
    - Shearer, Susan, 1925; MS214.007.005.00202 (Box 5)
    - Shedd, Dorothy, 1929; MS214.007.005.00203 (Box 5)
    - Sheehan, Margaret, 1945; MS214.007.005.00204 (Box 5)
    - Shelton, Howard, 1961; MS214.007.005.00205 (Box 5)
    - Sherman, Anna, 1961; MS214.007.005.00206 (Box 5)
    - Showstack, Ida, 1940; MS214.007.005.00207 (Box 5)
    - Siegel, Edith, 1928; MS214.007.005.00208 (Box 5)
    - Simmonds, Nancy, 1958; MS214.007.005.00209 (Box 5)
    - Simmons, Ruby, 1930; MS214.007.005.00210 (Box 5)
    - Simonds, Amy, 1958; MS214.007.005.00211 (Box 5)
    - Siu, Mary, 1960; MS214.007.005.00212 (Box 5)
    - Sjoberg, Mabel, 1923; MS214.007.005.00213 (Box 5)
    - Skelton, Winifred, 1938; MS214.007.005.00214 (Box 5)
    - Slota, Stacia, 1946; MS214.007.005.00215 (Box 5)
    - Smart, Kathryn, 1963; MS214.007.005.00216 (Box 5)
    - Smigliani, Lorraine, 1956; MS214.007.005.00217 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Betty, 1947; MS214.007.005.00218 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Catherine, 1941; MS214.007.005.00219 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Doris, 1963; MS214.007.005.00220 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Elinor, 1945; MS214.007.005.00221 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Inez, 1933; MS214.007.005.00222 (Box 5)
    - Smith, Lois, 1924; MS214.007.005.00223 (Box 5)
    - Southall, Eunice, 1942; MS214.007.005.00224 (Box 5)
    - Soroker, Eleanor, 1944; MS214.007.005.00225 (Box 5)
    - Spelman, Jeanne, 1950; MS214.007.005.00226 (Box 5)
    - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1953; MS214.007.005.00227 (Box 5)
    - Spencer, Gladys, 1942; MS214.007.005.00228 (Box 5)
    - Spencer, Laura, 1948; MS214.007.005.00229 (Box 5)
    - Spevak, Evelyn, 1924; MS214.007.005.00230 (Box 5)
    - Spiller, Gertrude, 1944; MS214.007.005.00231 (Box 5)
    - Spooner, Barbara, 1937; MS214.007.005.00232 (Box 5)
    - Sproat, Agnes, 1935; MS214.007.005.00233 (Box 5)
    - Stanwood, Marian, 1932; MS214.007.005.00234 (Box 5)
    - Staples, Ethel, 1936; MS214.007.005.00235 (Box 5)
    - Steeves, Lucinda, 1928; MS214.007.005.00236 (Box 5)
    - Stephen, Agnes, 1947; MS214.007.005.00237 (Box 5)
    - Stephenson, Elizabeth, 1934; MS214.007.005.00238 (Box 5)
    - Stevens, Flora, 1922; MS214.007.005.00239 (Box 5)
    - Stockman, Lela, 1926; MS214.007.005.00240 (Box 5)
    - Stone, Ethel, 1922; MS214.007.005.00241 (Box 5)
    - Stout, Walter, 1921; MS214.007.005.00242 (Box 5)
    - Stowe, Margherita, 1943; MS214.007.005.00243 (Box 5)
    - Strum, Edward, 1933; MS214.007.005.00244 (Box 5)
    - Stuart, Anastasia, 1921; MS214.007.005.00245 (Box 5)
    - Stuart, Genevieve, 1927; MS214.007.005.00246 (Box 5)
    - Stuart, Jean, 1943; MS214.007.005.00247 (Box 5)
    - Stubbs, Harriett, 1931; MS214.007.005.00248 (Box 5)
    - Sugrue, Winifred, 1931; MS214.007.005.00249 (Box 5)
    - Suh, Anna, 1963; MS214.007.005.00250 (Box 5)
    - Sullivan, Rita, 1966; MS214.007.005.00251 (Box 5)
    - Susmann, Anne, 1962; MS214.007.005.00252 (Box 5)
    - Sutherland, Dorothy, 1940; MS214.007.005.00253 (Box 5)
    - Svagdys, Brenda, 1956; MS214.007.005.00254 (Box 5)
    - Swasey, Florence, 1958; MS214.007.005.00255 (Box 5)
    - Taft, Francis, 1929; MS214.007.005.00256 (Box 5)
    - Tartakoff, Ruth, 1932; MS214.007.005.00257 (Box 5)
    - Teague, Mary, 1964; MS214.007.005.00258 (Box 5)
    - Tebaldi, Wilma, 1951; MS214.007.005.00259 (Box 5)
    - Tevrizian, Grace, 1928; MS214.007.005.00260 (Box 5)
    - Thaler, Victoria, 1947; MS214.007.005.00261 (Box 5)
    - Thomas, Helen, 1945; MS214.007.005.00262 (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Catherine, 1936; MS214.007.005.00263 (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Margaret, 1943; MS214.007.005.00264 (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Olive, 1932; MS214.007.005.00265 (Box 5)
    - Thornberg, Mary, 1959; MS214.007.005.00266 (Box 5)
    - Tierney, Mary, 1967; MS214.007.005.00267 (Box 5)
    - Tilletson, Elizabeth, 1947; MS214.007.005.00268 (Box 5)
    - Toland, Marjorie, 1927; MS214.007.005.00269 (Box 5)
    - Towski, Barbara, 1958; MS214.007.005.00270 (Box 5)
    - Tracy, Frieda, 1945; MS214.007.005.00271 (Box 5)
    - Trafford, Elise, 1945; MS214.007.005.00272 (Box 5)
    - Tranquillo, Marie, 1963; MS214.007.005.00273 (Box 5)
    - Troutivein, Mildred, 1930; MS214.007.005.00274 (Box 5)
    - Tsukada, Yuriko, 1944; MS214.007.005.00275 (Box 5)
    - Tufts, Marion, 1946; MS214.007.005.00276 (Box 5)
    - Usenius, Alma, 1945; MS214.007.005.00277 (Box 5)
    - Usher, Eunice, 1938; MS214.007.005.00278 (Box 5)
    - Vance, Christina, 1927; MS214.007.005.00279 (Box 5)
    - Variste, Mary, 1965; MS214.007.005.00280 (Box 5)
    - Verry, Herbert, 1958; MS214.007.005.00281 (Box 5)
    - Vibber, Leona, 1931; MS214.007.005.00282 (Box 5)
    - Violette, Dorothy, 1949; MS214.007.005.00283 (Box 5)
    - Voegtlin, Mary, 1956; MS214.007.005.00284 (Box 5)
    - Von Schirching, Susanne, 1942; MS214.007.005.00285 (Box 5)
    - Von Weiss, Anna, 1965; MS214.007.005.00286 (Box 5)
    - Wagner, Eva, 1946; MS214.007.005.00287 (Box 5)
    - Waldman, Margie, 1949; MS214.007.005.00288 (Box 5)
    - Walley, Lizzie Mae, 1947; MS214.007.005.00289 (Box 5)
    - Ward, Florence, 1925; MS214.007.005.00290 (Box 5)
    - Ward, Mabel, 1945; MS214.007.005.00291 (Box 5)
    - Watson, Mary, 1950; MS214.007.005.00292 (Box 5)
    - Weaver, Grace, 1928; MS214.007.005.00293 (Box 5)
    - Webster, Ann, 1940; MS214.007.005.00294 (Box 5)
    - Weisberg, Ruth, 1942; MS214.007.005.00295 (Box 5)
    - Weisberger, Electa, 1939; MS214.007.005.00296 (Box 5)
    - Weisman, Marjorie, 1954; MS214.007.005.00297 (Box 5)
    - Wendell, Elizabeth, 1925; MS214.007.005.00298 (Box 5)
    - Wesser, Anna, MS214.007.005.00299 (Box 5)
    - Weston, Donna, 1938; MS214.007.005.00300 (Box 5)
    - Weston, Dorcas, 1927; MS214.007.005.00301 (Box 5)
    - Westphal, Clarence, 1927; MS214.007.005.00302 (Box 5)
    - Wetherby, Una, 1936; MS214.007.005.00303 (Box 5)
    - Wheeler, Elizabeth, 1950; MS214.007.005.00304 (Box 5)
    - Whelan, Ralph, 1937; MS214.007.005.00305 (Box 5)
    - Wien, Janet, 1958; MS214.007.005.00306 (Box 5)
    - Wiggin, Barbara, 1946; MS214.007.005.00307 (Box 5)
    - Wignall, Loretta, 1954; MS214.007.005.00308 (Box 5)
    - Williams, Margaret, 1923; MS214.007.005.00309 (Box 5)
    - Wilman, Robert, 1946; MS214.007.005.00310 (Box 5)
    - Wilson, Frances, 1962; MS214.007.005.00311 (Box 5)
    - Wilson, Phyliss, 1964; MS214.007.005.00312 (Box 5)
    - Winder, Dorothy, 1952; MS214.007.005.00313 (Box 5)
    - Wing, Faith, 1925; MS214.007.005.00314 (Box 5)
    - Wingate, Reba, 1928; MS214.007.005.00315 (Box 5)
    - Winsor, Wilhelmina, 1922; MS214.007.005.00316 (Box 5)
    - Winters, Barbara, 1965; MS214.007.005.00317 (Box 5)
    - Witherspoon, Helen, 1939; MS214.007.005.00318 (Box 5)
    - Wolf, Pearl, 1939; MS214.007.005.00319 (Box 5)
    - Wolf, Ruth, 1948; MS214.007.005.00320 (Box 5)
    - Wong, Arlene, 1947; MS214.007.005.00321 (Box 5)
    - Woo, Susanne, 1930; MS214.007.005.00322 (Box 5)
    - Wood, Ann, 1954; MS214.007.005.00323 (Box 5)
    - Wood, Annie, 1948; MS214.007.005.00324 (Box 5)
    - Woolfson, Hilda, 1950; MS214.007.005.00325 (Box 5)
    - Worden, Mabel, 1930; MS214.007.005.00326 (Box 5)
    - Wright, Ledonia, 1956; MS214.007.005.00327 (Box 5)
    - Young, Mabel, 1921; MS214.007.005.00328 (Box 5)
    - Zaharias, Frances, 1949; MS214.007.005.00329 (Box 5)
    - Zamanigian, Beverly, 1962; MS214.007.005.00330 (Box 5)
    - Zeiderman, Lillian, 1928; MS214.007.005.00331 (Box 5)
  - Employee address cards and committee affiliations, MS214.007.002
    - Employee address cards, A-K, MS214.007.006.00001 (Box MS214 Shared 6)
      Cards include employee's name, address, department, and positions held.
    - Employee address cards, L-Z, MS214.007.006.00002 (Box MS214 Shared 6)
    - Employee address cards and committee lists, MS214.007.006.00003 (Box MS214 Shared 6)
      Employee cards include employee's name, address, department, and positions held. Stapled to employee card is their Notice of Withdrawel. Committee lists are organized by committee, and include names of committee members and dates.
  - General medical staff records, 1922 -- 1965; MS214.007.003
    - Medical staff, miscellaneous brochures, bylaw references, 1938 -- 1957; MS214.007.010.00035 (Box MS214 Shared 7)
    - Staff bylaws revision, 1938; MS214.007.010.00036 (Box MS214 Shared 7)
    - Medical staff organization and bylaws, 1951; MS214.007.010.00037 (Box MS214 Shared 7)
    - Medical staff lists, 1957 -- 1965; MS214.007.010.00038 (Box MS214 Shared 7)
    - Staff completed (active), 1962 -- 1963; MS214.007.011.00001 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Staff Executive Committee appointments, 1959 -- 1963; MS214.007.011.00002 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Waine, Hans, 1956 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00003 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Staff correspondence, 1927 -- 1962; MS214.007.011.00004 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Gibson, Count, 1963 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00005 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Gynecological staff, 1936 -- 1937; MS214.007.011.00006 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Tumor Clinic: Considerations, 1930 -- 1940; MS214.007.011.00007 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Unofficial appointments, 1957 -- 1962; MS214.007.011.00008 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Scientific staff, 1962; MS214.007.011.00009 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Optometrists, unofficial appointments, 1959 -- 1962; MS214.007.011.00010 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Podiatrists, unofficial appointments, 1961; MS214.007.011.00011 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Research labs, personnel, 1962 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00012 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Staff matters, leaves of absence, 1942 -- 1945; MS214.007.011.00013 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Application for appointment to medical staff, 1964; MS214.007.011.00014 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Tufts College teaching, 1959; MS214.007.011.00015 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Teaching program, Bingham, Kellogg, Boston University, 1951 -- 1957; MS214.007.011.00016 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Tufts Schools of Medicine and Dental Medicine, 1958 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00017 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Tufts University School of Occupational Therapy, 1960 -- 1965; MS214.007.011.00018 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Boston Dispensary property real estate, 1959; MS214.007.011.00019 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Land, Harrison avenue and Tyler street, 1941; MS214.007.011.00020 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Land, WPA street project, 1938; MS214.007.011.00021 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Staff residence, 1951; MS214.007.011.00022 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Insurance, fire, 1939 -- 1958; MS214.007.011.00023 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Land and buildings, staff residence, 1952; MS214.007.011.00024 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Land, miscellaneous, 1938 -- 1940; MS214.007.011.00025 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Plant, general correspondence, 1953 -- 1962; MS214.007.011.00026 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Insurance, general, 1963 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00027 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Group insurance, life, accident, and sickness, 1927; MS214.007.011.00028 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Inspection Certificates, 1958 -- 1963; MS214.007.011.00029 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Tufts College Medical and Dental schools, 1922 -- 1954; MS214.007.011.00030 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Teaching, Bouve-Boston Teaching program, 1953 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00031 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Insurance, boiler, air tank explosion, 1961; MS214.007.011.00032 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - NEMC committee reports (tissue), 1949 -- 1961; MS214.007.011.00033 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Office manual, 1938 -- 1964; MS214.007.011.00034 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Notes of Thomas Galligan, physio-therapy department, 1930 -- 1965; MS214.007.011.00035 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
    - Formulary of the Boston Dispensary, 1959; MS214.007.011.00036 (Box MS214 Shared 8)
- X-Ray department records, 1911 -- 1966; MS214.008; 2.4 Linear Feet